america what you doing i'm trying to figure out who's shit i'm finna fuck with next i feel like
conquering some shit bitch i'll tell your ass way y'all better stop sending all the missiles over
here y'all getting a little bit too close to them little launch tests y'all be doing on my mama i
don't like that shit on my dick i don't like that shit at all i feel like y'all trying to start some
shit with us korea shut the fuck up before i obliterate your ass uh-uh we ain't got shit to
do with that don't speak on korea the fuck you talk about the north we ain't know that over here
america that's your problem you always trying to bully somebody couldn't be me couldn't be me
and now you want to talk to me you want to talk to me and my people any kind of way we ain't going
for none of that shit then we take your motherfucking people and bitch we want them back your ass ought to
be in jail for what you did all your ass who has something to do with taking my goddamn children
africa girl what the fuck you doing here this is meeting for the country yeah and your big ass ain't
no country you a continent hoe so y'all ass took my people from all over my continent in every country
matter of fact nigeria come handle this hoe don't trip i'm finna call ogun now what's up
man look y'all arguing about the wrong shit what we need to be talking about is the money
the dinero pesos america y'all owe us 3,456,789,656,315 yen and we want our money back
y'all broke ass owe everybody some money who broke you see me blinking who broke who is you even in
them with the galactic federation yeah and if they don't get they money they gonna turn
y'all ass every which way but loose mm-hmm i had already got on a payment plan with them
last year you don't be paying it that's why they been sitting all them ufo's down here
you stay blind trying to tell people to my spabaloons my spabaloons don't even look like
that them people come to get they bread y'all think they finna come for real i done told
y'all broke ass